gchats.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

  *   * Gchats is committed to protect your security and your personal details when you use Gchats Website, Services and Products on the Website. Here you can find details on how and why we protect your details and what we do with your information. Please check back our Privacy Policy for any changes and amendments in the future. 

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

1\. What we collect?
    We may collect the following information: 
    * Identifying you, every time you visit this Website, use our services and products.
    * Record data relating to our products and license usages.
    * Record your order details.
    * Record the details which you submit using the forms provided in this Website.
    * Contact information including email address.
    * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.
    * Store users information on our servers, when you are using product demos provided in this website or our hosted chat services.
    * Other information relevant to customer surveys and statistical procedures.
2\. What we do with the information we gather
     We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 
    * Internal record keeping.
    * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
    * We may use the information to monitor products license usages.
    * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
    * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
    * We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
    * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
3\. Security
    We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
    we do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.
4\. Links to other websites
    Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
5\. Your personal information
    We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the contact us page found on this Website. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

Last updated: 9 Jan 2012 

  * Enter your e-mail address

Remove Subscribe

  * Customers portal has been launched. Now you can manage your orders, licenses and subscriptions in your control panel. To access the portal, click on the customers link and login with your previously registered email address.

May 31, 2012

  * \- Userlist sort ordering feature added in the admin panel.

\- Media player music and video uploading feature added.

\- Microphone echo when using handsfree.

\- Unicode usernames couldn't login in the.

\- Unicode usernames appeared incorrectly in the logs and online list.

\- Blocked members could remove the gag by changing the rooms.

\- Double enter on login brought to an empty room.

\- Improvenet: Auto reconnect to separate streaming server disconnections.

\- Improvenet: online members file now allows more flexibility on styling this file.

April 28, 2012
